<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!--
    Document   : cholomachine2.xml
    Created on : 29 de noviembre de 2011, 10:25 AM
    Author     : ricardo
    Description:
        Purpose of the document follows.
-->

<data>
	<contenidos>
		<contenido>
			<titulo>History</titulo>
			<texto>
			Cholo Machine from 1xxx has dabbled in Ecuador in the sale of shoes, and now
			We are pioneers in the sale catalog. Today our footwear can be found in any city
			country through the sale catalog.

			Cholo Machine is a technologically and administratively structured to meet a market
			increasingly competitive and demanding, which is dedicated to the sale of shoes, which
			Value added is the only guarantee we can offer against a product of excellent
			quality, and 6 cozy shops that we make available to consumers. In this way we can
			to offer products with high technology, value added and better customer service.

			If you want the ultimate in fashion is in the right place thanks to our web portal can now be at
			day with our new collections.
			</texto>
		</contenido>
		<contenido>
			<titulo>VISION</titulo>
			<texto>
			Reaching out to fit all Ecuadorians, offering quality comfortable footwear
			and imposing fashion through the different brands we distribute.
			</texto>
		</contenido>
		<contenido>
			<titulo>MISION</titulo>
			<texto>
			Using modern and functional premises available to the public we offer a service and
			a high quality product as well as contributing to economic development in several families with our
			system catalog sales.
			</texto>
		</contenido>
		<acordion-contenido>
			<img-path>imagenes/ac1.jpg</img-path>
			<acordion-texto>
			ZigTech technology. This technology is in the sole that is in a zig zag. The interesting thing about this 
			new technology created by Reebok is that it distributes the energy generated by the impact of the heel to 
			the sole, which reduces wear on the legs and generates a forward momentum.
			</acordion-texto>
		</acordion-contenido>
		<acordion-contenido>
			<img-path>imagenes/ac2.jpg</img-path>
			<acordion-texto>
			This is the evolution of the New Balance 903, designed for mild pronators. It's a great shoe competition and 
			due to its low damping in the front of the same is advised for very fast runners.
			</acordion-texto>
		</acordion-contenido>
		<acordion-contenido>
			<img-path>imagenes/ac3.jpg</img-path>
			<acordion-texto>
			If you love all things 1970's, have a look at these classic shoes for running, coming straight from PUMA Archive. 
			Whether you use them to run or to stay in motion, you'll be comfortable and well.
			</acordion-texto>
		</acordion-contenido>
		<acordion-contenido>
			<img-path>imagenes/ac4.jpg</img-path>
			<acordion-texto>
			The Nike Air Pegasus is potentially the most emblematic of the history of running, this year marks the
			25 anniversary of the Pegasus model created by Mark Parker in 1983.
			</acordion-texto>
		</acordion-contenido>
	
	</contenidos>
</data>
